<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>investment on m 傳媒</title>
    <link>http://www.4stack.pro/tags/investment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in investment on m 傳媒</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 08:25:38 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.4stack.pro/tags/investment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What Are We Saving For? Using assets in retirement – Commercial Equity Release schemes</title>
      <link>http://www.4stack.pro/blog/20191126-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 08:25:38 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.4stack.pro/blog/20191126-10/</guid>
      <description>What Are We Saving For? Using assets in retirement
The most common type of wealth-holding by older people is home ownership. A mortgage-free home represents a lifetime of accumulated savings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong property investment dives in Q3 as Asia Pacific markets moderate</title>
      <link>http://www.4stack.pro/blog/20191126-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 08:20:38 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.4stack.pro/blog/20191126-07/</guid>
      <description>The Hong Kong protests hit the financial hub’s commercial real estate investment during the third quarter of 2019, with transaction volumes falling 32% year-on-year to US$2.7bn, according to Real Capital Analytics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSCI生效 台股將爆量</title>
      <link>http://www.4stack.pro/blog/20191126-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 08:20:38 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.4stack.pro/blog/20191126-08/</guid>
      <description>美中有望簽訂第一階段協議，亞股昨（25）日紅光滿面，但台股遇</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Best Cities in Asia to Buy Real Estate</title>
      <link>http://www.4stack.pro/blog/20191126-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 08:19:38 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.4stack.pro/blog/20191126-06/</guid>
      <description>When buying offshore real estate, your choice of city is perhaps even more important than picking a country.
Real estate markets are driven by local factors like employment opportunities and housing supply.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Buy a property in Japan</title>
      <link>http://www.4stack.pro/blog/20191126-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 08:12:38 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.4stack.pro/blog/20191126-04/</guid>
      <description>You can register your ownership by submitting application forms to the Legal Affairs Bureau.
Examination at the Legal Affairs Bureau will take one or two weeks after submission. After the procedures of the registration are completed, you can obtain the certificate of your ownership.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>